{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864567.870199, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c1cd7de2-752c-11ea-b6e5-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c1ce83d8-752c-11ea-9f08-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c1ce84c6-752c-11ea-8b8f-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864568.1527522, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c1f89b1c-752c-11ea-8f87-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c1f89c1e-752c-11ea-a0d4-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c1f89c70-752c-11ea-a059-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864568.4277601, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c2229192-752c-11ea-9b06-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c2229298-752c-11ea-ba5d-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c2229306-752c-11ea-aea8-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864568.701667, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c24c5d10-752c-11ea-a820-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c24c5e1e-752c-11ea-b84e-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c24c5e78-752c-11ea-bbcf-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864568.9790819, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c276b19e-752c-11ea-91d1-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c276b29a-752c-11ea-9a88-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c276b2f4-752c-11ea-b347-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864569.280628, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c2a4b4c6-752c-11ea-9407-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c2a4b5f0-752c-11ea-8bb3-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c2a4b64a-752c-11ea-b943-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864569.562526, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c2cfb85e-752c-11ea-9471-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c2cfb96c-752c-11ea-87f0-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c2cfb9ba-752c-11ea-bafd-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864569.832906, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c2f8fa1e-752c-11ea-ad9b-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c2f8fb2e-752c-11ea-a4c4-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c2f8fb88-752c-11ea-912d-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864570.1072562, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c322d6e2-752c-11ea-bd8d-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c322d7f0-752c-11ea-a969-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c322d84a-752c-11ea-97f5-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
{"sourceUrl": "example.com", "sourceName": "example", "sourceDate": 1585777414.515401, "lastUpdateTime": 1585777414.515401, "needUpdate": true, "typeOfInfo": "QA", "isAnnotated": false, "responseAuthority": "", "hasAnswer": true, "targetEducationLevel": "NA", "extraData": {"hello": "goodbye"}, "dateScraped": 1585864570.3794482, "questionText": "What is COVID-19 ?", "answerText": "Coronaviruses are a large family of viruses .", "containsURLs": false, "questionUUID": "c34c5f62-752c-11ea-8c2d-9801a78e188f", "answerUUID": "c34c6066-752c-11ea-936b-9801a78e188f", "exampleUUID": "c34c60ca-752c-11ea-af22-9801a78e188f", "topic": "topic1"}
